[Music]
Heat
up here.
[Music]
Hey everyone, thanks for joining us. I'm
Ted R. John Kuryaku is joining me. We
are here for the drogram show. Uh we're
going to have something exciting. We're
going to figure out regular normal times
to broadcast this live. So for people
who like to watch live and participate
in the live chat, there will be a
predictable time. uh we we will announce
that next week and uh you'll be able to
to plan your whole life around us. You
know, quit your job, get a new job. Uh
anyway, it's Thursday, May 22nd and
thanks for joining us. Um so, John, uh I
think Ted, I've got to interrupt you. Go
ahead. Uh, I'm I think your sound uh
your sound is not good. And I'm I'm
hoping it's not mine, my connection, but
uh it sounds kind of like an accordion
playing. Oh, that's not
good. Um, that's not good. Uh, now you
sound okay. You sound okay to me.
Okay, good. Well, let me tell we were
going to start with this uh uh Israeli
embassy uh double
murder. Um oh, it looks like it might be
just me. Okay, let me know. Let me know
if my sound cuts out and I'll I'll
figure something out. But anyway, last
night, last night, two Israeli embassy
staff members um were murdered outside
of a museum I had never heard of, the
National Jewish Museum in See, I've
lived in Washington for 43 years. I've
never heard of this museum, but that's
true. They were coming out.
Yeah. And a guy named uh Elas Rodriguez
uh was apparently waiting for someone to
come out. They weren't specifically
targeted. He apparently planned to shoot
the first people that came out of the
museum. These were two Israeli uh
embassy staff members. He killed them
both. They were um apparently soon to be
engaged to be married. and he shouted uh
free free Palestine as they were as they
were
um uh taking him away. And just a moment
ago, I got a push notification from the
New York Times saying that he's been
arraigned and charged with first-degree
murder times two. And he shouted in
court, "I did it for Palestine. I did it
for Gaza."
You know, I I'll tell you too, Ted, the
one thing that has really surprised me
about this is reading the comments on
the Washington Post article and the
comments at Unilad, which is an online
online kind of light news service.
Um, there are no pro-Israeli comments,
period.
There just are none. People are saying
things like thoughts and prayers,
thoughts and
prayers, or this was 3,000 years in the
making, or that's okay because right
after they were getting married, they
were going to go look for property in
the West Bank. Um, it's of
course it's of course wrong to to
murder, right? We we we yell about the
Israelis all the time. Um, this is just
as wrong. But I understand why it
happened. And and I when I say that, I
hope people understand me. I condemn
this double killing
unreservedly, but I understand why the
anger, the fury boiled over
it. I couldn't agree more. I mean, look,
um this is not like if we're trying to
emancipate the uh the people of
Palestine, this isn't this is not the
way you do it. Now, I have to admit I
would have different feelings if the
victim were a high-ranking IDF general.
Um, and I would feel that I would agree
a legitimate target. These are low-level
embassy staffers. They're nobodyies. And
you can certainly argue that nobody
should work for the state of Israel. But
I mean, really, in in the real world,
these are what they used to call in
World War II, the little fish. Very
little fish. Minnows. Yes. Um, and so it
it doesn't do any good. Um it it feeds
into the narrative of uh BB Netanyahu
and his government and it says you know
who they've been crowing. Here we go.
This is the anti-semitism we've been
talking about. Uh there's no evidence
whatsoever that the that Mr. Rodriguez
if if he is indeed the killer um is
anti-semitic at all. All we know is that
he favors the liberation of Palestine.
And it's irresponsible to suggest
otherwise. He may well be anti-semitic.
Uh, if so, I'll talk about that. We
don't know anything about this guy. No,
we don't know anything. So, but but I
mean, but I but you know, just last
week, John, I wrote my syndicated column
was with the headline, how Zionism
causes or encourages anti-semitism. And
to me, this is almost like an
illustration of it, right? I mean, oh,
it's like that's it literally when you
if you conf if you set up a if you
conflate anti-semitism and anti-ionism
and then you operate behind the scenes
to like basically have people deported
uh you know you you have them their
their diplomas removed they're expelled
they're suspended their lives are ruined
and it seems like and then or you have
like shadowy campaign donors I mean
sorry cor uh uh donors to colleges and
universities calling behind the scenes
and getting campus groups banned and so
on. It feeds into these ant classic
anti-semitic conspiracy theories about
like Jewish conspiracies. So, it's, you
know, I mean, it really is dangerous to
Jews. I mean, these these guys are
dangerous. They're they're a menace to
Jews. Um, and a lot of Jews get that and
they don't like it. Um, and and I mean,
and I know quite a few who really don't
care for it. You know, Ted, not not the
last time I was in New York, which was
yesterday when I saw you. Um, but the
time before, a few weeks earlier, Yeah.
I had lunch with a buddy of mine in some
nice restaurant, and there was a a table
next to us, two elderly women, turned
out to be both in their early 80s. They
looked much younger, but they were
listening to our conversation. And of
course, we were talking about Gaza and
the West Bank and, you know, these
lunatics who were who were members of
the Israeli parliament or I'm sorry, the
Israeli cabinet. And one of them said,
"Excuse me, I couldn't help but to um to
overhear your conversation." She said,
"We're both Jewish, and what you're
talking about is exactly what we fear.
We fear that Benjamin Netanyahu and the
right-wing extremists that he surrounds
himself with are pushing the world into
anti-semitism. It's not that
Palestinians are anti-semitic, which of
course they're very, but that's a whole
different uh conversation. She said that
Netanyahu has led the country so far to
the right that the rest of the world is
turning against it. and it's easy to
transition from being
anti-Zionist to being anti-semitic. And
that's exactly what they fear. And I
said, I have to agree. It would never
even occurred to me that have it would
not have occurred to me 20 years ago
that we would be in this position where
the Israeli government is so
rightwing that it might actually lead to
its own destruction.
Yeah, that's I mean it's funny, right,
that you mentioned that. Like I remember
up until like you say about 20 years ago
my take and I'd been to Israel a number
of times was like I would come back and
I'd say you know their government and
back then was far to the right of where
Israeli society was. Um I felt like you
know it probably half of the Israeli
people really wanted to see an
independent free Palestinian sovereign
state. Sure they wanted to so they don't
have to deal with it anymore. Exactly.
But also, but also there were a lot of
liberal Israelis who just generally felt
like it was the right thing and it it's
a fair thing. Um, and it's what needed
to happen. And I mean that those people
are still there, but there's fewer of
them. The whole situ the the the
government has pulled them to the right.
They've helped they the situation's been
radicalized. No doubt October 7th
radicalized the situation more. Uh
people times war makes societies stupid
as we saw after 911. Um so uh you know
people just they just become idiot they
just become idiots and um yeah no I mean
this is it's really frightening and I
wonder at some point when will this
stop? I
mean I mean he's he's corrupt.
He's terrible prime minister. If you
only care about the state of Israel and
its future and you want his state of
Israel to be successful, Netanyahu is
not helping, you know. Got that right.
Got that right. And this is a guy who's
been prime minister longer than any
other person in the history of Israel.
And he has never won more than 27% of
the vote. Never. Now that's of course
attributed to the fact that Israel has
so many political parties and such but
but if oh that is absolutely correct who
wrote that roofie thank you for that is
absolutely
correct. Apac, you know, I just for my
own curiosity, Ted, I I started doing
some research into Apac, and Apac was
this
like it was like this fringe
uh lobby group from when it was founded
in the in the 1950s until the 19 the
early 1970s. Nobody paid any attention
to it. Uh it it wasn't terribly um busy
on Capitol Hill. And then when Richard
Nixon guaranteed the security of Israel,
everything changed. And it changed right
under our noses. And people didn't even
notice it. I gave a speech at the
biggest conservative synagogue in
Manhattan back
in
2011. Tahareth Jeserun. It was called.
Gigantic place on Park Avenue, no less.
And
um it just happened to be what was
called Israel Bond Day. I had never
heard of this, but every every year once
a year, one Saturday, um in every
synagogue in America, they sell bonds.
And the bonds, their Israeli government
bonds that are used to supplement the
funding of the
IDF. So, in the 30 minutes before my
speech where the rabbi got up and said,
"Oh, today's Israel bond day. Pull out
your checkbooks, everybody. Let's buy
some bonds and help the IDF."
$500,000 in the 30 minutes that that we
were waiting for people to finish
writing their checks.
$500,000. Okay, this is one synagogue.
Now imagine this is happening in every
synagogue in America and Canada on the
same day.
That's crazy. And then on top of that,
you've got the billionaires that are
that are financing Apac. And then you've
got the campaign contributions coming
from a from Apac that essentially buy
most of America's politicians, at least
at the federal
level. It's just not a good situation at
all. And I'm not sure how we go back
from this. Well, it's the blank check,
right? No, no nation state should get a
blank check from the United States of
America. And if I were president, that
would be the first thing I'd say. Yes.
And why And why is And why is the IDF,
you know, begging for for for cash when
they're getting four part of the four
billion dollars a year from the US
foreign like that's not going to
healthcare? No. The IDF advertises on TV
in Florida. Call this toll-free number
and show your support for Israel. I
never saw such a thing. I happen to be
in Miami and they run these TV ads. Call
this number with your credit card and
support the IDF. It's like, are you
kidding me? It's bizarre. It is. Yeah.
It's like I don't Can you imagine like,
you know, like I don't call up call this
number and support the the national the
national armed military of Bolivia. Like
what? Why? Yeah. It's like what? What
are you talking about? If come on,
you're Bolivian. You love Bolivia.
Support our right to defend ourselves
Colombians. You know what? Yeah.
Yeah. Very strange. And so it's it's
interesting to me that um you know,
obviously news out of Gaza is is never
there's never unfortunately a dull
moment. A dull moment would be, you
know, a beautiful thing at this point.
But uh this this news hit just as um
really credible reports of mass
starvation are starting to they're all
over the place. They're unavoidable.
They're all over mainstream media. It's
not just the Gaza Health Ministry. Uh
it's the AP. It's the New York Times.
It's the Guardian. Um you know, children
are in particular children are dying of
of starvation. And this is because
Israel won't allow food, medical aid,
water, fuel into Gaza, into the Gaza
Strip. It's been months. Trucks are are
sitting there. I don't even know, by the
way, how the trucks what kind of food it
is that it's able to maybe even survive
all this time waiting unrefrigerated
presumably. I I guess it's dry goods, I
assume. But still um you know the and I
think the the Israelis are starting to
feel a little bit of heat here. Um I
mean at a certain point the heat is
coming from the from the Europeans.
Um it's it's the British, the French,
the Germans that are saying, "Hey, hey,
you guys have gone too far. We're going
to freeze aid right now until you let
this food in." That has not been enough
to force the Israelis to actually let
the food in. They've let in two trucks.
two trucks to feed two million people.
The Irish have had the guts to stand up
and and break relations with uh well, I
don't know if they broke relations so
much as they froze relations and asked
the Israeli ambassador to leave. Um but
the Israelis aren't going to do anything
until Donald Trump tells them enough is
enough. And I'm not seeing that
happening. Although there are there's
certainly some, you know, there's some
some word behind the scenes that um
Donald Trump seems to no longer quite be
marching to BB's drummer. Um he's
probably I mean by most accounts, right,
the rumor mill is that Netanyahu is an
unpleasant, very demanding partner uh to
American leaders. And uh that doesn't
seem like a recipe made to work with the
Donald. Um, and uh, you know, I mean, I
think that Donald probably feels quite
rightly that he's done quite a bit for
Israel already. He's he's he moved the
uh, US embassy to Jerusalem, something
that the the hardliners have wanted for
years. He's sent them tons of money. Uh
but I think he has kind of he you know
he's he's a showman and he knows that
the the optics of what he seems to be
supporting are really bad and it's the
same really bad that the that Joe Biden
who is now lies completely discredited
uh by the Jake Tapper book which came
out yesterday which I'm about of the
third about a third of the way through.
Bombshells one after the other. Are you
reading it? Yeah, it's I mean so I
expect you know I mean I expected that
most of the meat like in the Bob
Woodward books you don't really have to
buy those books because the most of the
meat turns up in the Washington Post not
so in the Jake Tapper stuff because
there's meat on every single page and I
feel compelled to write something about
this um and I feel com I feel compelled
to take a swipe at Jill Biden
um because she's Lady McBth. She's Lady
McBth. That's exactly right. That's a
great way to put it. She knew from the
first time he ran, or not the first time
he ran, but from his first term, be from
the campaign before his first term that
he was demented.
And she led him around, let him on
stage, let him off stage, covered for
him. I mean, this is like uh Edith
Wilson and Woodro Wilson all over again,
right? However, it's worse because
Woodro Wilson came into the White House
in
1913 sharp. Um he didn't leave that way,
but you know, Ronald Reagan, came in
sharp. Ronald Reagan, sharp guy, smarter
than I gave him credit for at the time.
As it turns out, when you read his
letters, you're like, "Oh, actually, he
was a very thoughtful guy." But you know
and and it's not right to leave a
sitting president in office for a year
or two when you know his mind is mush.
It's not right. But this is this is a
whole different level. This was a cover
up. Yeah. From they elected a guy that
they knew was already scenile. He was
already suffering from dementia. Um from
day one from day one of the campaign. I
mean, according to the Tapper book, his
basically his mind blew up when Bo died
2015, right? And they ran they ran him
five years later. Um, so he wasn't
better by then, right? Aging doesn't
look No, no, no. I mean, of course,
obviously, it's not like always a
straight line, but it's just But there
was a general downward trajectory. I
mean, some of these stories are
absolutely stunning. Um, and you know,
he talks about, for
example, one week into his
presidency, Biden goes to Capitol Hill
at the invitation of um of uh Nancy
Pelosi to talk about the Democratic
agenda and just could not vocalize why
he was there, looking around, smiling at
people, and she took over to say, "Well,
here's here's the Biden agenda. This is
what we're going to do." He was he was
worthless, useless the one week into his
presidency. So, we need to blame Joe
Biden. We need to blame Nancy Pelosi. We
need to blame Kla Harris. We need to
blame whoever it was that happened to be
head of the DNC. They all were part of
this conspiracy to cover up for him. And
then he had the unmitigated gall to run
for reelection.
It's unbelievable, right? and and behi
and behind the scenes, right? Everybody
knew better. So, there's this group of
five um you know, cronies whom are
described as the pilot bureau by Jake
Tapper in the book who are basically
these insiders that you've never heard
of. Um who, you know, are basically
campaign adviserss and staff. Um and
they basically were running they've been
running the country. Now, I assumed it
was like, oh, it's I really thought it
was Tony Blinken was running the
country. Yeah, turns out he really
wasn't. Um, you know, turns out, you
know, Lloyd Austin, you know, there's a
reason why Lloyd Austin thought he could
go awall because they needed him. No,
you gonna tell it's an it's a no-show
job like in the Sopranos. It's like I
mean, they they none of them were
talking to the president and you know,
nobody needed to talk to the president
because the president really wasn't the
president. Um he was he was only around
from like 10 to 4 by all accounts. If
something had happened, you know that
that famous ad, you know, there's a
phone in the White House. There's a
crisis at 3:00 in the morning. Who's
going to pick up that phone? Not Joe
Biden. If it was after 5:00 p.m., he
wasn't picking up that phone. Couldn't
pick up that phone. It'd be scary if he
picked up that phone. and and like and
all these like things that we thought
were just gaffs like uh oh yeah like
I'll go we'll go to war over Taiwan. No,
it turns out he was like bonkers. He
literally didn't know the policy. He's
literally adultled. I mean, I guess it's
in some ways it's the ultimate it, you
know, the wisdom of the founding fathers
is exhibited by the fact that we just h
the country didn't burn to the ground
over the last four years and here we are
still talking. So, I guess it's a great
system. It's it's president proof. Um,
you know, I kind of said that about
Trump's first term, too. Um, but I but
like now this is unparalleled in terms
of of political scandals. There's I
don't I mean not only I'm gonna say I
don't think there's ever been anything
close in the last 250 years. I don't
know that any other c you can look at
many other countries that have had
something like this. I think you have to
go to like ancient Rome with like you
know the emperor who who who turned his
horse into a god. You have to find that
level of of corruption and insanity. Um,
I don't think, you know, there were
there there were there were thoughts
that uh, you know, Brej wasn't really
all that great by the late 70s. It
wasn't like this. I mean, no way. And
besides, they had a poll at Bureau that
they admitted to, you know, okay, the
the general secretaries adult. That's
okay because we have these 12 guys
around them that are going to run the
country. We don't have it here. And and
also in this book Yeah. Also in this
book are admissions that you know the
cabinet members would go a year without
ever seeing the president. No meetings,
no nothing. It was he just wouldn't see
his cabinet members. He probably
wouldn't have even known many of his
cabinet members. Yeah. Apparently that's
a that was a main that's a recurring
theme in the book, right? where he he
meets people whom he's known for years
and I don't think he has that disease
where you don't recognize faces. Um, you
know, he's just he's just was suffering
from dementia. Um, it's you and I were
talking Go ahead. I'm sorry to interrupt
you. You and I were talking a couple of
days ago about um about the George
Clooney oped in the New York Times. And
I remember when we were still on on uh
Sputnik saying, "Why would George
Clooney of all people write an op-ed for
the New York Times now on this issue?"
Well, now we have an answer because
Biden flew out to uh California for this
major fundraiser, major like the biggest
fundraiser in the history of the
Democratic party. Um and uh and he
didn't have the foggiest idea who George
Clooney was. And he's known Clooney for
years and Clooney was one of his primary
fundraisers. No idea who he was. And
finally, one of the aids said, "Oh, Mr.
President, you remember George." and and
uh and Biden says, "Thanks for your
support, George." Like, "No, he doesn't
have any freaking idea who this guy is
that's just raised $10 million for him
in one night." And And who is George
Clooney, by the way? And who is George
Clooney? Like, everybody in the world
knows who George Clooney is. And then
Clooney talked to who was it? Was it
Katsenberg? It was somebody big. Yeah.
Um and said, "I'm gonna I'm gonna write
this oped." And he's like, "Blow, please
don't do it. Please, please." No, I got
to write this off. And and he went and
did it. And then just today, I uh I read
about about the whole uh Taylor Swift
thing where they sent um oh, what's her
name? Pretty Woman. Um Julia Roberts.
Julia Roberts. They sent Julia Roberts
to convince
um Taylor Swift to make an endorsement
because she had heard from her Hollywood
friends that the president is, you know,
just an empty mannequin.
And uh and Julia Roberts apparently
talked her into it. This this is a bad
look from absolutely every angle for the
Democratic Party. This is just terrible.
They tried to pull one over the eyes of
the American people.
and why why would any voter trust you
now when you tried to do something like
this? And so what's interesting to me
too is in reading the book um Kapper,
you know, he he repeatedly keeps coming
back to the polls that show that the the
public just wasn't on board. None of
this worked, right? That's why Biden
lost or why he would have lost and how
Harris lost. Um, and you know, it it's
fascinating to me that even though they
propagandized, they had control, so much
control of so much influence.
Nevertheless, the American people sat in
their living rooms in, you know,
wherever and they looked at the TV and
they're like, I'm not buying what you're
selling. That guy is too old and he's
out of it and he he he can't do it and
I'm not going to vote for him. and the
and and just the answer is no. And the
arrogance of the powers that be inside
the Democratic party to think no no no
we'll we'll convince them. I mean
there's that I mean I'm sure you've
gotten to this point. It comes up pretty
early on where he t they you know at one
point one of Biden's veteran pollsters
calls in and says oh well you know I'd
like to run some polling numbers uh some
internal polls on the age issue. Oh, no.
We don't we don't need to we don't need
any polling. The the pilot bureau tells
him, "What do you mean you don't need
any polling? You always need polling.
It's a presidential campaign." No, the
decision's been made. Biden's and
remember, we always kept hearing this.
Biden beat Trump. He's the only Pearson
who's ever beaten Trump, which is a
stupid true. It's stupid logic. Um I
mean, you know, Bernie Sanders probably
would have beaten Trump by more. Sure.
Um any number of other candidates might
have beaten Trump and um you know it's
just sort of like it's like and and so
what I mean yeah exactly I mean you
could go back to the last time we had a
situation like this which were uh you
know these Grover Cleveland the Grover
Cleveland's in Grover Cleveland's out
Grover Cleveland comes back and you know
there's these rematches with Benjamin
Harrison one time it goes Benjamin
Harrison's way but the next time it
doesn't go Benjamin Harrison way, right?
So, it's like you don't it's like big
deal. I mean, that's like I mean, you
know, you would think that like in this
day of big data, right? Most money in
political campaigns gets spent on data,
not on ads. And and so in this age, you
would just think that like, okay, we
need numbers, we need facts, we're we
need to respond to facts. The these guys
around Biden and the Democratic party,
it was like a religion. It was like a
religious cult. It was blind faith. It
was not real. They they they just I mean
they were out to lunch. How could we I
mean and and now we're you know it's
it's hilarious. They spent the last four
years talking about Trump and how Trump
how bad Trump was while Biden was
president. And I would say, "But Trump's
not the president. Let's talk about
Biden." Well, now it's like that this
has happened. They're saying, "Well, you
know, Biden's not the president. Let's
talk about Trump." Yeah. They just want
to talk. It's it's so it's it's
maddening because they're still
insulting the intelligence of the
American people. They are. And you know,
it might they might be more convincing
if if Biden had ever stood for
something, you know, like for
example, Biden was always one of these
middle-of the road guys. He he may early
on have been kind of racist. He was
against uh uh integration through
busing. He was the primary author of the
the terrible uh criminal justice bill of
the 1990s.
Um if if he if he was, you know, a
Democratic version of Ronald Reagan or
if he was a John Kennedy figure who
actually stood for something, right? And
and people could rally around him and he
inspired passion. All right, then maybe
I could see ah for old times sake, we're
gonna cover up for Joe. Yeah, but he was
none of those things. None of them I
remember they covered up for too, right?
They covered up for sure. Yes, exactly.
Was a god. People had people had his
portrait up in their homes. They thought
that grandparents did. He I I used to
see him in garage sales when I was a
kid. people people thought that he had
saved them from dying of starvation. Um,
you know, I mean, he created the New
Deal, the the social safety net as we
know it. And so, like, you know, if he's
getting a little long of the tooth and
he's going to violate like, you know,
the the the old the gentleman's
agreement that we only serve two terms.
Well, there is Hitler and Tojo to
consider, right? That's right. I mean, I
get that. Let the man finish the job.
Yeah. Let him finish the job. And then
in 1944, okay, he's kicked months later,
right? So, they shouldn't have really
should not have, but still, and the war
was pretty much won by that point, but
you know, they didn't know what they
were going to do. What what we're going
to let Henry Wallace be president? So,
right. Exactly. So, I mean, one of my
heroes. I I love him. I get that though.
I get it. Look, I mean, that's the other
thing, right? That Joe Biden as national
grandpa, he was always an [__] I
mean, you know, I mean, always from when
he was young. Yes. From when he was a
young man, he was an [__] Day one.
And like the sympathy for him. I mean,
it's like, okay, well, you know, he's
had tragedies in his life. No question.
Um, you know, if you live long enough, a
friend of mine said everybody has
tragedies in their life. Um, and that's
right. And it's like I don't make light
of what's happened to him, but that
doesn't get get him off the hook for any
of this. Um, you know, and and I don't I
don't understand the sympathy for him.
Um, you know, I don't understand the
cover up for him. I don't understand the
idea that only he could save us from
Donald Trump. There was, you know, in
2020 there was an incredibly impressive
lineup of Democrats up on that debate
stage when Joe Biden was coming in
fourth in primaries, right? I mean, if
we really look at this, right? I mean
Pete Buddha Judge was very impressive
even though he was wet behind the ears
and you know but he was an impressive
guy. Um Amy Clolobachar totally
respectable better than Joe Biden the
governor the governor of Washington
state Cy Booker too.
Yeah there were lots in fact remember
there were so many Democrats running for
president
they had to separate them into two
nights. Yep. Elizabeth Warren.
Eight. Yeah. There were like 18 of them.
and um you know and Elizabeth Warren I
mean who could who on earth can look at
Elizabeth Warren and and Joe Biden and
say yeah I'm going to take him like what
on earth are you thinking she's she was
as fast asleep she was smarter than he
was wide awake you know I mean it's it's
completely it's
inconceivable I mean it must be
maddening for people like her
oh my god their counsel they all have to
shut
It's a mafia. Yeah, they do. It is. It's
a mafia. It the the fix was in from the
beginning in in during the 2020 campaign
when Brian Becker and I uh still had our
show. I I know I've said this before,
but it's even more appropriate now.
Um there were three incidents that that
so bothered me that we we spent, you
know, a quarter of the show talking
about it. months Biden was giving a
speech and and his eyeball started
bleeding, right? And it the the whole
white of his eye became red. He had some
kind of like surge in his blood
pressure. It's an old man thing. This
happens when you're an old man. Your
eyeball just spontaneously starts
bleeding. Number one. Oh, just awesome.
Number two, he's giving a speech and
he's, you know, h he's talking and
giving a speech and his teeth fall out
and he catches them. He catches them and
he puts them back in his mouth. I was
like, "Oh my god, I didn't know he wore
dentures." And like a decrepit old man,
his [__] teeth fall out of his mouth.
Number two. Number three, it was just a
week or two before the Iowa caucuses and
he goes out on stage in Iowa to give a
speech, but there are really bright
lights. The media are all there, bright
lights. He gets confused because he
can't see beyond the lights. And he
gives the entire speech with his back to
the
audience. It's like, seriously, this is
who you guys want as president. There's
nobody else in the Democratic party
that's bit better than this. This is
what you want. Yeah. That's just great.
Yeah. No, you know, thank you for
reminding me of the tea thing. I'd
forgotten that. I mean, there are so
it's on YouTube. There are so many
outrageous incidents, right? I mean, you
know, I always I always like the one
where he's calling out for the dead lady
whose funeral he had attended. She was
killed in the car accident. He went to
the funeral and he's like, "Is she here?
Where is she? Stand up. Stand up for
everybody. Round of applause." It's
like, "She's dead. You went to her
funeral a week ago." By the way, you
know who I'm believing right now? I'm
believing Tara Reed. I comp I was never%
sure, but now I do 100% sure. I believe
her. I do. Oh my god.
Just saying. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean,
you gota we've got to revisit that, you
know. Um we actually have to. Yeah. I
mean, you know, we we can get her on the
show. We can talk to her. Um Oh, yeah.
She texts me every once in a while.
Yeah. Yeah. She's Tara Reed. For for
those of you who don't remember, Tara
Reed was an intern in Joe Biden's Senate
office and she she said that he got
handsy with her one day um in the
stairwell.
Yeah. In the stairwell. Nobody believed
her. She ended up her word, not my word.
She ended up defecting to Russia. Yeah.
And um Well, you can't really defect to
Russia anymore, but Okay. No. No. And
then like four months after she defected
to Russia, she went back to Oregon to go
to her daughter's wedding and then went
back to Russia again. She was defecting
to the Pacific Northwest. Then she was
undefecting. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, this
is a good question. We have a question
from Road Beef. When I was with the
agency, did I ever write or see a cable
about another world leader in a similar,
let's say, condition as Biden finds
himself? No. Never. There was a That's a
great question. There was a question
situation immediately after the Iraqi
invasion of Kuwait where the Amir of
Kuwait had a nervous breakdown, but that
wasn't dementia. He just he I mean his
country he'd been overthrown. His
country was invaded and he just cracked.
So um
other than that, Robert Mugabi was super
old. He was like 90 something years old.
Yeah. Yeah. He was quirky, right? Yes.
by the end. Super quirky. Yeah, he was
kind of pride me a little bit. I don't
know. Yeah. Yeah.
Gudafi the last few years. Maybe he had
a lot of pressure. How about like
Suarto?
He became quite murderous toward the
end, right? I don't know. That's a great
question. Not in my experience. A
lunatic. Duterte is a lunatic. And I'm
very glad that he's in the dock at the
Hague right now where he belongs. That
is where he belongs 100%. Um, yeah. So,
I mean, I'm gonna I'm looking I mean, I
can't tear I can't stop reading this
book. It's just, you know, it's a page
turner. It is a page turner. And if
you've been following this thing, I
mean, you know, it's like it's like sort
of like every time I I pick it up, I'm
like, I can see clearly now the rain is
gone. I mean, I always had a pretty good
sense, but it's like there's so much.
And it's like, oh, okay, so we're not
all insane, so I get it now. You guys
were gaslighting us. And this is, by the
way, what gaslighting is. Gaslighting
has come to mean, uh, you know, just
lying like, oh, like, you know, my my
girlfriend gas lit me and she said she
was going to the store, but she was
going on a date with another guy. That's
not gaslighting. That's just lying.
Gaslighting is where is where you are
trying to pretend, you know, gaslighting
is where you try to make someone insane
and question their own sanity. Um, you
know, where it's like you break into
their house, you move all their lamps to
the other side of the room, and you make
it look like no one was ever ever broke
in. That's gaslighting. It's kind of
stupid, actually. I'm not sure it ever
works. Um, you know, but I heard that
back in the Cold War, the KGB, Did you
ever hear stuff about this? Like the KGB
used to do stuff like that? like they
would break into like an American
journalist's like uh I heard the
Israelis the Israelis do it now to
American diplomats. What do they do?
Rearrange the furniture. Take shits in
all your toilets.
They do. It's so incredible [__]
How weak would your sanity have to be in
order to to be to start questioning like
I'm pretty sure some I didn't that's not
my [__] you know? You would know
someone's been there. Yeah, that but
that's what they want. They want you to
freak out.
Yeah.
Well, well, someone's saying, by the
way, that she didn't use the word
defect. The media did. Ah, okay. Okay.
We'll see. Um, all right. So, there's a
lot here. Um, there's more. Um there's
the uh there's also the uh the big
beautiful bill which is Did you know
it's actually called legally? I did not
know that. I did not know that until
yesterday.
The big beautiful bill act. Yeah. The
big what a stupid name. I
mean, okay, so you know, Donald Trump
never ceases to to surprise, but I mean,
it's like I mean, the country feels I
mean I mean, it's not just him. It just
feels like we're becoming so
infantilized. And I do feel like it's
both parties who are doing it to us and
the media is going along with it. And
and it's like it's every detail. It's
sort of like how on every station they
all copy the Fox News um you know Gerand
approach like you know bearing down on
the east coast a storm you know with
with winds sweeping the city you know
it's like supertorrm Sandy this is a
beef I have superstorm is not a
meteorological term it was hurricane
Sandy period it was a hurricane yes it
was damaging lots of hurricanes are
damaging
But what makes it a super storm? What is
the measure? I hate that storm of but
it's the same idea. Super supertorrm.
Like it's like a black exploitation
film.
You know, somebody mentions um Forson
Sebastian Thomas Massie is the only
Republican with a spine. Amen to that.
I've mentioned a couple times he's a
friend of a friend um and we've gone to
a half a dozen ball games together. He
is a delightful guy to go to a ball game
with. Delightful. And he always brings
like junior aids with him who can't
afford to go to a ball game and sit in a
decent seat. He's a really good guy. Um,
and he's the only one who's a
real he's a he's a true believer. like
he believes that he has thought through
these these issues and that his position
is right and that you've got to be
consistent. You can't just go with the
political winds one way or the other.
And if this is what he believes, then
that's what it's going to be. And I have
deep respect for that. Deep respect.
Yeah. No, I I And to tell you the truth,
don't fault that. I cannot think of many
Democrats that I could say that about. I
I would say that about Jim McGovern from
Massachusetts. because by God he's been
pro Snowden and
pro-Ass. But he's pretty much the only
Democrat I would say that about Massie
and McGovern, the two of them. Yeah. All
right. Before we I I have something I
want to ask you about that we talked
about before the show. But first,
there's a a viewer question from
Abdullah Alatar. So what do you think of
plan of of the plans of Israel's plan
for Gaza which is basically to push most
of the population if not all of the well
all of the population to a tiny uh uh
part of the of the strip not
coincidentally along the border wall
with Egypt. Yeah. Here we go again.
Right. Oh what a coincidence like the
spring of 2024. Um, and they want to and
then meanwhile the IDF is to occupy the
rest indefinitely while they I continue
to I assume detonate and demolish all
the buildings. Um, what do you think the
demolitions are all about? I mean I I've
been curious about that. Like why not
just um you know if you have a business
a bu a building that survived even if
you plan to seize the the strip why not
keep it? Yeah. I I think it's it's all
about punishment. You know that we
should point out too that what the
Israelis are planning
um is is the very definition of
genocide. Genocide doesn't have to be
just murder of a people. Forcible
relocation of an entire people is also a
definition of genocide in international
law.
And so the fact that not just the United
States but most of the Western world is
willing to sit by and or sit back rather
and and let the
Israelis commit a
genocide. It's it's unacceptable. Like I
said a few minutes ago, only the Irish
of all people, the Irish have the balls
to stand up to the Israelis and say,
"This is wrong and we're not going to
let you do it or we're going to do our
part to stop you from doing it." Nobody
else has the guts to do that. They ought
to because the genocide is unfolding
right before our very eyes. Has been has
been for a long time. Yeah. And
so I I I think that the Israelis believe
that they can get away with it because
the United States isn't going to stop
them. And the the the British and the
French and and the others have said,
well, if you continue doing this, then
we are going to have to give serious
consideration to issuing a very strongly
worded letter, you know.
God forbid. Yeah. Yeah. So a quick
reminder to people who are enjoying the
show and even if you're not enjoy
enjoying enjoying the show the show
please subscribe please follow it really
makes a difference uh it makes a
difference between it being viable or
not viable. Uh so and you know this is
true about any show like this but you
know definitely just just hit that
button as it by the way subscribing on
YouTube costs you not one penny. Um uh
subscribe and uh same thing on Rumble.
Uh you paid support is always
appreciated on Rumble but you you can
became a become a paid follower for $5 a
month but it's uh it ain't it definitely
it's it's free. Also hit like on
everything that you see if you Yes,
please. Please do. Much appreciated.
Okay, so um before the show you texted
me that you had like uh some dish on um
America's uh favorite Russian president.
So let's hear it. Yeah, I have another
podcast called Deep Focus with John
Keryaku. And this morning I interviewed
Dr. Peter Kousnik, who is one of the
country's leading Russia experts and a
and a genuinely good guy on top of it.
We're going to release it tonight. But
he said something that just knocked my
socks off. He said that um oh he just
got back from Russia. He mentioned
off-handedly and he goes to Russia with
some frequency. He speaks at a lot of
universities there and meets with people
from Russian think tanks etc etc. And he
said that he went with Oliver Stone.
They are very very close friends. and he
went with my friend Ray
McGovern.
So I I'm like pretty close friends with
Ray McGovern and Ry never mentioned that
he was going to Russia with Peter and
Oliver Stone. So he said that
uh that they went to the Kremlin and
uh Vladimir Putin said, "Oh yeah, let me
let me meet with Oliver and Rey."
uh not Peter, but Peter has been
criticizing the the Russian uh invasion
of of uh Ukraine Ukraine, excuse me. And
he uses the word
invasion as do we. But uh but Oliver
Stone and and God bless him, Ray
McGovern went in to Putin's office and
met with Putin for 40 minutes. Wow. I
don't know what was said, but I'm going
to call Ry tonight and ask for a
readout. And I I thought this was
absolutely great. Absolutely great. Now,
the the point of our conversation in
part was
uh why isn't why isn't Vladimir Putin
doing as Donald Trump orders him to do,
right? This has to be a mystery for
Trump. Trump says, "Come to the table."
He expects Putin to come to the table.
And Putin said, "Forget it." We talked
about the talks in uh in Turkey the
other day where where Trump said, "Well,
if Putin goes to uh to Turkey, then I'll
go to Turkey." Well, Putin didn't care
one way or the other if Trump was going
to go to Turkey. And Putin never had any
any idea
um
uh whether or not he would even have
been welcomed to Turkey. And and fresh
sub. Thank you. I love how Mr. Stone
gave Putin Dr. Strange Love on DVD. They
actually watched it together. Peter
talked to us about that today. They He
just happened to have Doctor Strange
Love and he asked Putin in this
conversation, "Have you ever seen Doctor
Strange Love?" Putin said no. He says,
"I actually have a DVD." And he pops
this DVD in and they sat there and
watched Doctor Strange Love together. I
hope he brought the right zone. You know
how there's different zones for DVDs?
That's right. That's right. Yes. Yeah.
It craziest thing. So, I gotta call Ray
tonight and say, "Ray, you gotta you got
to lay this on me." What the heck
happened? What did Putin say? Oh my god.
Very, very interesting to me. But, you
know, he said something else that was
also very interesting here in the United
States, especi especially in the
American media. Putin is a
dictator. He's a strong man. uh it's a
monolithic government. None of that is
true. Peter said Peter said that
um that uh you know there are there are
insiders to both the right and the left
of Putin. There are hawks and there are
doves and he has the same kind of
balancing act as any American president
would have. And so, you know, whether
Donald Trump just gets up and says,
"Putin go to the negotiating table."
That's not going to be that's not enough
to make Putin go to the negotiating
table. He has his his own domestic
politics to worry about. That's exactly
what this is about. I I have thought
from from all all along. Yeah, even if
not even if secretly uh in his heart of
heart Putin agreed verbatim with
everything that Trump wants u and I
suspect they're pretty they're not that
there's not a lot of daylight right now
I think between where Trump I mean I
think Trump basically sees things
Russia's way um and uh you know he's he
wants the he wants the war to end and
basically I think as if Russia if uh
Trump could snap his fingers uh Russia
would probably get everything that it
asked for except for formal recognition
of the loss of Crimea and the Donbos,
but they would, you know, but but
basically would get everything. Um, but
Putin can't and I asked Peter about
that. I said, "Is that what's going to
happen?" Right. Yeah. Right. I asked
Peter about that. I said I said, "The
Ukrainians are going to lose Danetsk and
Luhansk and Crimea, right?" and he said,
"Yeah, they're going to lose it. That's
it. That's the only way this ends."
There's a there's a a possible ceasefire
line that's almost perfectly
um along the border. Yeah. Of donut skin
lines. That's going to be That's what it
looks like to me, too.
I mean you can see I mean and it's and
all you know the the idea that like we
keep hearing like you know Putin wants
to take over all of Ukraine. I mean,
okay, in the beginning days of the war,
I think if if I think the idea was like,
well, you know, Ukraine might be weak
and we're going to go
like and if it goes and Zilinski blows
away, great. But like it didn't go that
way. So, you know, like fine, never
mind. But I mean, he the Russians got
what they came for and they don't want
to occupy the ethnic Ukrainian of
Ukraine. They'd be a pain in the ass.
They'd be dealing with resistance of all
sort. It would be arrestive populace. No
one needs that. That's a pain in the in
the butt. Um and but the I and also the
idea that they're going to invade Poland
and the Baltics. I mean, these guys are
all smoking crack. That's not Yeah,
that's not in Russia's interest. The
idea is Russia wants land. Really? Have
you looked at a map? That's the one
thing they don't need. They don't need
land. They've got land. Land is like not
a problem for Russia. Yes. It's not
Germany trying to get to the sea.
Yes, indeed. Yes, indeed. I agree.
It's It's so absurd. Um anyway, so any
other tasty tidbits from the Putin uh
behind the scenes? Like what was he
was very droll? I read I read the Philip
Short. I've heard that. Yeah, I've heard
that. You know, do you remember the the
uh the big dinner? It was the 10th
anniversary of the founding of RT
uh back in
2015. I was invited to that dinner. It
became it became kind of famous because
Jill Stein was there, Jesse Ventur was
there and and uh General Mike Flynn was
there. I was invited to that dinner. I
was invited to sit at that table. That's
awesome. And my sentencing judge would
not release my passport to me. She
refused to allow me to go.
I was out I was out of prison, but she
said, "Oh, no. You're not going to
Russia." So, I didn't go. Well, Putin
showed up at the dinner and and went to
the table to shake hands. He he didn't
stay for the dinner. He was there for
about 10 minutes, but he shook
everybody's hand. I would have had my
chance to meet Putin. Yeah. I want I
want a picture of me with Putin for
sure. Oh, yeah. Oh, it'd be fun. I mean,
yeah. I mean, he's he's he's I think
he's absolutely fascinating. Um, for
sure. And I al I think he's a very
impressive guy, too. Um, you know, I I I
don't share his politics. Uh, but I do
get I understand why Russians vote for
him. I do. Yeah. I I agree. Especially
after the Yeltson experience, it's that
was extremely traumatic. Chaos. And And
we installed that idiot. You know, we
did. We did. And you know, the the
negotiation reportedly was that we would
have no objection to to Putin replacing
Yeltson so long as they didn't prosecute
Yeltson for corruption. So, we exceeded
to to Putin.
Well, I mean, yeah, to to quote Robert
her, uh, I think Boris Yeltson would
have come off as a kindly, well-meaning
alcoholic,
um, unable
to, you know, there's no mena with that
guy, although I don't know if that's a
part of Russian law. Um, you know, he
say that again. It's like, God, what a
Yeah, like we George HW Bush really
[__] up. In 1991, we had the
opportunity to tr to help the Russians
come in for a soft landing from
communism and uh and turn them into an
ally and and they wanted that and
instead we [__] them and uh it's and
and it's like, you know, I mean, they're
just getting over it now and and and now
we still want to do it again. I mean,
it's we're the worst really. Um Yeah, we
are.
Um, yeah, we have a question on about
start tree. Do we want to answer that?
So, there's a Yeah, you know, Peter
Kousnik touched on this as well. Oh, I'm
sorry to interrupt you, Ted. Peter
touched on this as well. Listening and
not watching. Uh, what are what are our
thoughts on the new START treaty
expiring? Cap on NES will end. Will
there be a new arms race?
Yeah, Peter says the answer is a clear
yes.
Um he he
he said
that that uh Russia
had 150
nukes before this start treaty was
signed. They destroyed a hundred of
them. That made it 50. Once the treaty
expires, there's no reason why they
wouldn't replenish what they destroyed,
especially with with relations with the
US being in the state that they are.
That he was told the Russians want to
get back up to 150 and then 200 nukes.
But he said that the Chinese are doing
the same thing, that they've got about
150 nukes now. They're going up to 200.
And there are plans by 2050 to go to
2,000 nukes. Wow. Uh and nobody's not
only is nobody talking about, you know,
renewing start, they're not talking
about inviting the Chinese in. There
aren't even any plans for
discussions. Nothing. So to answer your
question about whether it's going to be
a new arms race, I think the answer is
yes.
What a waste. Oh, whoa, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. Jay, Jay, we don't
like Putin. We never said we liked
Putin. No, I don't like Putin. I respect
Putin as a leader. I think he's good at
what he does,
but no, I Yeah, I'm against American
imperialism just just like I'm against
Russian imperialism. I am against and
Israeli imperialism.
Yeah, I'm Yeah, I'm the same. Look, I
agree with you, John. I don't need I
mean look here's the thing is I can
objectively find someone impressive um
you know like okay I I met Fidel Castro
I found him impressive um and that
doesn't mean that I admire what you know
that I would vote for the regime the
autocratic of Cuba that he had but was
he an incredibly impressive man with an
incredibly impressive history absolutely
as a as a figure of you know I mean I
think, you
know, you don't have to uh I mean, I
don't know. It's kind of like we were
talking about Joe Biden earlier. He's
not an impressive man. Even you know,
people are trying to make him
impressive. That's that's absolutely
right. And even though I now on the
other hand, I agree with the
infrastructure bill that Joe Biden
pushed through in 2021. I thought that
was a good bill. Um I think we need
infrastructure. That was great. I can
agree with something that he did and
still say he's a mediocre intellect. Uh
he's a he's a he's a bad person and he
was uh you know really not an impressive
guy at all way, shape or form. I think
Marjorie Taylor Green is impressive in
some ways. I mean you know you you have
to be able to be objective about people
and and you know it's kind like separate
the art like I would I think James
Wood's politics are stupid. He's a great
actor. Those two things I could live
with. Clint Eastwood. I I think I didn't
like his his RNC appearance. I love
Clint Eastwood movies. I'll see anything
that he directs. You know, I'm sorry. I
think we It's like there's this thought
that like you have to if you say
anything nice about someone, it means
that you agree with them and that you
like them.
Yeah, I agree with everything you just
said. Except Marjorie Taylor Green.
Well, she is kind of impressive
considering where she came from. I mean,
you know, she's a she's a she gives hope
to skanks everywhere. Yeah. Well, there
you go. Well, the other one's worse.
Lauren Boowbert. Oh my god. True, true.
I Yeah, I have Oh, this is a good
question from Castro. Where does William
Burns end up when Trump appoints new CIA
director? Uh, well, yeah. I mean, Burns
is gone. Burns. I wrote an op-ed when
when Burns was named CIA director said
saying this was the best possible choice
for CIA director because you need an
adult in the room to smack these guys
down and tell them no when they want to
do something stupid. And Burns not only
was a career ambassador, having been
ambassador to what four, five, six
places, he was also the deputy secretary
of state, which is the the official
that, you know, runs the day-to-day
operations of the State Department. My
guess is that Bill Burns is going to get
a gigantic book advance and he's going
to end up on the board of some think
tank here in Washington and live happily
ever after. I think in terms of of a
career, it's probably over. I think he's
going to enjoy his retirement.
He's got to be I'm 60, so he's got to be
70 72 maybe.
Oh, I got to put this one up. All right.
Yeah. So, I agree with you. Yeah. All
right. Let's So, uh, one of our posters
says, "Hey, John, I'm a local embassy
staffer. Let us know if either of you
want to speak more regarding the event."
Uh yeah. So absolutely. Yes. Drop us a
line. Um you can contact me through my
website
raw.comcont. Um John, I don't know if
you have a way to be reached that way.
Yeah, you know what? My my email address
is no secret. I think I think it's even
in my uh on my website. It's it's easy.
It's jkuryakume.com.
So thank you for that. Thank you for
that. We'll look forward to hearing from
you. And if you're lying to us, we will
kill you. Um, so
after all, we've been lying now for five
for five years about about Joe Biden. No
more. No more.
Um, so, oh my god, this is so fun. Uh,
this is like open mic Friday. Uh, do we
see China invading Taiwan in the next
four years? Well, John, you're you're
the expert here. I'm going to say no
faking way. What do you think? Yeah, I'm
gonna say no. And I don't I don't want
to give the Chinese too much credit. Uh
but the Chinese really don't have an
imperialist history besides Tibet. You
know, they've they've fought a couple of
border skirmishes with the Indians over
the years. They fought a border skirmish
with the uh with the Vietnamese back in
the 70s, but they but they really are
not quick to use military um uh
action. I I will
say
that there were reports last week when
five Indian jets were shot down that it
was not the Pakistani Air Force that did
it, that they were actually Chinese
pilots. I don't know if that's true or
not. I doubt that. But I I just I Yeah,
I I I can't I can't see a a war on on
Taiwan. It's just there's no up there's
no upside to it. There really isn't. It
it it could lead to world war and it's
just not worth the trouble. Sean Ryan,
dog on Shawn Ryan canceled me two weeks
ago. I was getting ready to fly to
Nashville to do it. Yeah. And his
producer said that I'm just uh not
important enough. Sorry. Oh, well that
can happen. Oh, I I do want I want to
know the answer to this question. Any
spooky DARPA experiences for people who
don't know what that is? That's the what
is it? The Defense Advanced Research
Project. Yeah. Something agency agency.
Uh so that's that's like the high tech
cool like gadgets and stuff. Oh yeah.
Yeah. Everything that's futuristic to
tell you the truth. DARPA and what DARPA
does is so highly classified that almost
none of us at the CIA were cleared to
know any of it. So I had literally zero
interaction with DARPA. Nothing. The at
the CIA most of the the cool spy
gadgetry that we used we just bought off
the internet.
I actually is it true I read I read at
one point that um some someone uh that
there was what was that store?
Um, there was a chain store that sort of
like sold spy type gadgets. You know
what I'm talking about. Oh, there was
there was the spy shop. Yeah. Well,
that's there were like a half a dozen of
them. Uh, and and much of it was just
from Radio Shack. We would just go buy
the the parts at Radio Shack and put
stuff together.
That's hilarious. Yeah. You know why?
Because it's so it's so much cheaper
just to buy it than it is to reinvent
the wheel, you know?
Like in
Pakistan, I I used more spy gadgets in
my six months in Pakistan than I used in
the rest of my entire career combined.
And all of it but one gadget we we
purchased online. There was one that we
made and it it took about it took about
two days to put it together. So you're
saying it's not like it's not like the
Bond films like, "Hey James, we have
something you'll really like.
Yeah. And it is it's something that you
really like, but we didn't we didn't
have any of that, unfortunately. I I
told a story a couple of times where um
on my first day at the CIA uh at lunch,
uh all of us met our new bosses and our
bosses took us to lunch. And the CIA has
a couple of interior courtyards. And I
happen to glance out the window and I
see this robot mowing the lawn. And I
said, "Hey, that robot's mowing the
lawn." And my boss said, "Yeah, we
invent a lot of things here." And um and
uh you know, that's one of the things
they're not exactly sure what to do with
it. They develop this technology, but
they don't know what to do. So, it's
just mowing the lawn. Like five years
later, the Roomba is released. And that
was the robot that I saw mowing the
lawn. They just converted it into a
vacuum cleaner and called it the Roomba.
and they license the technology.
That's awesome. Um, yesterday I saw an
interview with Elon Musk where he was
saying that he expects uh there to be
humanoid and uh robots, androids um that
will be within the next few years. Uh
the demand he said, will be off the
charts. And you will walk down the
street within the next five years and
you'll see one walking down the street
like and you'll be like, "Who's that
non-dude dude?" or what's that non-dude
dude people but you know how people are
you know how people are they're gonna
want to have sex with them and if you
can't if you're gonna spend that kind of
money on a robot you're going to want to
have sex with it and if you can't then
nobody's going to want to spend that
kind of money there's a great there's a
great movie about that by the way highly
recommend the comp uh it's called
companion it's currently out I forget
which streaming service maybe either max
or or Netflix uh but it's one of those
anyway highly recommended it's about
that. It's about sex bots, basically.
Um, and it's very, very
clever.
Um, all right. Well, uh, I'm trying to
think, is there anything else we failed
to hit here, John? We This I love the
hodge podge, you know. Um, I do, too.
It's fun. It's totally fun. Uh, let's
see. A whole spade of comments came in
here. All right. So, should we do Yeah,
I kind of like I gotta say
sex I kind of agree like uh Well, would
sex bot Okay, question. Will sex bots
solve the incel problem?
Probably.
Well, that's that's good.
Didn't say say we're going to send our
incelss to some other country. He said
this like two weeks ago. We're going to
send our incelss
to like some Middle Eastern country or
something. I don't remember. America's
loss is Qatar's gain. Um like really I
mean by the way
in Arabic it's it's
but it comes from down here. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't I don't have that in my in my
vocal cords.
Uh Jay asks another question about uh
what what accepting the guttery jet will
entail. And oh yeah, I mean they're
gonna they're going to have to literally
take it apart and then put it back
together. I just read an article. Yeah,
I just read an article the other day
saying that the jet's worth 400 million
and to take it apart and put it back
together is going to be another 600
million. So is it really worth it? It
reminds me of the 1966 Barracuda that I
bought for $4,000 and put $25,000 into
it. Um, not really the best buy,
although it was a great car. Um, that's
really car. Yeah, it was it had the
biggest piece of glass ever put into an
American sedan. Um, you know, good for
the good for the and it was not a slow
car um by any means. It had a 340 V8.
Uh, it was it was you could out you
could out race pretty much anything.
Um, all right. So, and then I guess
should we feel u Oh, oh, I got to ask
you this. Do you believe for one
that Joe Biden just found out that he
has cancer?
Oh, come on.
An 82y old man not getting a prostate
exam since
2014. Come
on. Whatever whoever his doctor was
should lose his license if what they're
telling us is true. I don't believe for
a second is true. Well, also he's the
president, right? I mean he is man he
the president is automatically sir it's
time to go to Walter Reed for your
annual physical and and and the PSA test
is is part of that workup right always
nothing extra is required blood and they
just send a little bit of it over to the
PSA people right so and we know that
they did it for Trump in in 2017 18 19
and 20 so they stopped doing it in 2021
like ah we don't need that right you
know like magic hold the mayo No. Hold
the PSA test. I don't buy it for a
second.
Nope. Don't buy it. No. And and and what
would their defense be? Would their
defense be with like, okay, we lied to
you about everything else, but he really
didn't. We're telling the truth about
his PSA levels. Come on. Yeah. That's
the problem. And uh it is true. I should
say that someone uh someone else is
putting up that and uh the Dilbert guy
has it as well. Todd Adams, who I know,
a friend of mine, Adams. Yeah. And uh
you know, I worked with him at United
Media. I was his editor. Um and I'm And
you know, seriously, it is it's
horrible. And uh of course, the thing is
we're in such a a an environment. I have
to admit, Scott's a troll and he's a
prankster and it's I wouldn't put it
past him to be to for this to all turn
out to be like a lie. Um, I mean, like I
I had I had friends that like we we've
talked about like how the Pulitzers have
gotten totally woke, you know, like you
have to be, you know, an a trans Native
American, you know, this and that to
win. And and I was like, you know, I
need to claim that I've transitioned.
And we literally were plotting how to do
that. And like I, you know, I wouldn't
change anything. I just be the same guy.
But I'm like, now you have to call me
Tadina or whatever. Uh, and just just to
see if like as a prank to to expose
their stupidity. Um, but you know,
probably it probably wouldn't land and
trans people would be mad at me. They
I'd be the new JK Rowling. No one needs
that. Right. Right. But without her
money.
So, oh my god.
So, here we go. So, this is hilarious. I
just hope Pus Joe is going to be okay.
Y'all ain't cool like
that. I don't know. I mean, would I care
if Hitler got
cancer? Not really. I mean, I'm not
going to pretend false sympathy for a
person who is a very bad person. Um, you
know, I mean, look, I I I'm against
cancer. I hope cancer goes away. Yeah,
should stop bugging the human race,
including Joe Biden. But um you know, I
mean, he's a guy who literally laughed
his ass off for, you know, for for two
years of of of genocide in Gaza. I mean,
of course, maybe he wasn't. Maybe he
didn't really know, but but he was
always like a militant Zionist. That
goes way back. Oh, yeah. He's always
been a ardent Zionist. Yes. So, yeah.
Yep. All right. I think I think we're
probably uh probably gotta wrap it up
here. Let people be. Yeah. Thanks for
joining us everybody. Really appreciate
it. Please thanks for joining us.
Reminder if you're just little
housekeeping. Please subscribe. Please
follow, please like, please send to your
socials. Please tell all your friends.
Please tell your mom, your dad, your
cat, your dog. Appreciate it. And uh I
have a new book out. What's left? Please
buy it. really appre actually it's
selling pretty well for a for excellent
a book about the radical left. So uh you
know excellent people seem to be to be
enjoying it. So we'll be back soon.
We'll let you know. Watch the socials.
Bye everyone.
Bye-bye.